我
i
先生们，我们到了！
And there we are, gentlemen!
¡Y ahí estamos, señores!
我们来了，Nueva Fa Estudio 先生！
And there we are, Mr. Nueva Fa Estudio!
¡Y ahí estamos, señor Nueva Fa Estudio!
开始 将会发展
that starts that is going to develop in
que arranca que se va a desarrollar en
非常好，瓦雷拉先生，一切都井然有序，一切井然有序。
Very nice, Mr. Varela, everything in order, everything in order.
Mucho gusto señor Varela, todo en orden, todo en orden.
一切平静，很好，很好。
Everything calm, good, very good.
Todo tranquilo, bien, muy bien.
今天是一个特别的日子。
Today is a special day.
Hoy es una jornada especial.
这是一个特殊的日子，国际足联的日子，这是选拔周，实际上是两个选拔周。
It is a special day, FIFA date, it is selection week, two selection weeks actually.
Es una jornada especial, fecha FIFA, es semana de selección, dos semanas de selección en realidad.
我们从埃扎时代就已经在这里了，但国家队正在走上一条道路
We have been here since Eiza's period, but the national team is on a path
Nosotros estamos desde el periodo de Eiza, pero la selección está en derrotero por
到处走走。
Going around.
Dando vueltas.
不同的地方，我们带来了一位特殊的客人。
Different places and we brought a special guest.
Diferentes lugares y trajimos un invitado especial.
没错，隔着屏幕。
Exactly, through the screen.
Exactamente, a través de la pantalla.
我们没有把它带到这里，因为它必须在那里，而是通过屏幕。
We didn't bring it here because it has to be there, but through the screen.
No la trajimos acá porque tiene que estar allá, pero a través de la pantalla.
很特别。
Very special.
Muy especial.
非常特别，我们将在几分钟内分享，仅此而已，仅此而已，仅在几秒钟内，仅此而已
very special we are going to share in minutes nothing more in minutes nothing more in seconds nothing more
muy especial vamos a compartir en minutos nada más en minutos nada más en segundos nada más
我们与 Leonel Scaloni 先生录制的内容是与 Leonel Scaloni 先生的愉快聊天
A content that we have recorded with Mr. Leonel Scaloni is a nice chat with Mr. Leonel Scaloni
un contenido que hemos grabado con el señor Leonel Scaloni es una linda charla con el señor Leonel Scaloni
如果这是假的我会问他，你想问他什么？
If this were false I would ask him, what do you want to ask him?
si esto fuera falso vivo yo le preguntaría ¿Usted qué le quiere preguntar?
我们已经记录下来了。
We already recorded it.
Ya la grabamos.
事情就是这样，不得不说。
That's how it is, it must be said.
Es así, hay que decirlo.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
¿Por qué no?
就是这样。
It's like that.
Es así.
你会喜欢什么
What would you have liked
¿Qué le hubiera gustado
接下来的说明，也许当他抛出我刚刚和我的兄弟朋友谈论的内容时，我并没有这样做。
The next note, maybe I didn't do it when he threw out what I was just talking about with my brother friend.
la próxima nota igual no yo lo hice cuando tiró lo que hablaba recién con el amigo hermanos
说到阿根廷足球，我不得不说里斯特。
With Argentine football I had to say Riestre.
Con el fútbol argentino tenía que decir Riestre.
啊，你问他关于阿根廷足球的事，对吧？
Ah, well you asked him about Argentine soccer, right?
Ah, pues usted le preguntó sobre el fútbol argentino, ¿verdad?
但奇怪的是怎么说我问他
but it's strange how to say that I ask him
pero es raro como decir que le pregunto
好吧，但我们是在粉饰人们。
Well, but we are whitewashing people.
Bueno, pero le estamos blanqueando a la gente.
如果我们不做假直播的话。
If we don't make a fake live.
Si no hacemos un falso vivo.
我不会对你撒谎。
I'm not going to lie to you.
No le voy a mentir.
我们在 15 分钟内完成了现在...现在...现在你将会看到它
We did it in 15 minutes And now... And now... And now you're going to see it
Lo hicimos de 15 minutos Y ahora... Y ahora... Y ahora la van a ver
现在我必须把它传递出去，嘿，国家队的教练会看到这个，这样人们就可以来体验这个和另一个
and now I have to pass it on, hey, a coach from the national team is going to see this so that people can come to live this and the other
y ahora tengo que pasarlo eh que van a ver un entrenador de la selección esto para que la gente vaya llegando al vivo esto y el otro
一个轻松、非常轻松的国家队教练。
a relaxed, very relaxed national team coach.
un entrenador de la selección relajado, bien relajado.
是的，与航班问题无关，他说
Yes, not so much with the flight issue, which he said
Sí, no tanto con el tema del vuelo, que dijo
我们向他询问了飞机的问题。请记住，我们是在米尔顿的中心。
We asked him about the issue of airplanes. Remember that we are in the middle of Milton.
Le preguntamos por el tema de los aviones Acuérdense que estamos en el medio de Milton
米尔顿，米尔顿。
Milton, Milton.
嗯，我喜欢...
Well, I like it...
Bueno, me gusta...
你会怎么说呢？
How would you put it?
¿Usted cómo le pondría?
现在我要考虑姓氏……我会给他举个例子……我想要布兰坎·罗伯托。
Now I'm going to think about the last name... I would give him for example... And I would like Blancán Roberto.
Ahora voy a pensar el apellido... Yo le pondría por ejemplo... Y Blancán Roberto me gustaría a mí.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
它必须是更多的东西......如何？
It has to be something more... How?
Tiene que ser algo más... ¿Cómo?
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
啊，那就轮到我淋湿了。
Ah, then it's my turn to get wet.
Ah, entonces me toca mojar.
飓风西蒙娜，就像我的母亲一样。
Hurricane Simone, like my mother.
El huracán Simone, como mi madre.
我母亲的名字是西蒙娜。
My mother's name is Simone.
Mi madre se llama Simone.
飓风西蒙娜。
Hurricane Simone.
El huracán Simone.
这是一个与其解释性质有关的参考。
It is a reference that has to do with its interpretive nature.
Es una referencia que tiene que ver con su carácter interpretivo.
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
这太可怕了，是有史以来最坚固的房间。
This is terrible, the strongest room in all of history.
Este es terrible, el cuarto más fuerte de toda la historia.
但它还没有登陆任何地方，对吗？
But it hasn't made landfall anywhere yet, right?
Pero no tocó tierra en ningún lado todavía, ¿no?
在哪里？
Where?
¿En dónde?
印刷品。
The print.
La estampa.
我是打印面，对吗？
Me for the print side, right?
Yo para el lado de estampa, ¿no?
I 为打印面。
I for the print side.
Yo para el lado de estampa.
嘿，我还是重复一下我刚才说的话，我告诉过你，我不记得这个有没有，我希望有一场飓风。
Hey, I still repeat what I said a while ago, that I told you, I don't remember if this was there or not, that I would like there to be a hurricane.
Che, igual repito lo que dije hace un rato, que se los dije, no me acuerdo si estaba esto o no, que a mi me gustaría que hubiera un huracán.
碰巧你是一个喜欢夸张事实的朋友。
You happen to be a friend of extravagant facts.
Pasa que usted es un amigo de los hechos extravagantes.
你也想参与战争。
You would like to be in a war too.
A usted le gustaría estar en una guerra también.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
飓风、海啸和地震，碰巧发生地震必须非常幸运
Hurricane, tsunami and earthquake, it happens that an earthquake has to be very lucky
Huracán, tsunami y terremoto, pasa que terremoto tiene que tener mucha suerte
我在洛杉矶发生了 6.1 级地震
I had an earthquake in Los Angeles of 6.1
Yo tuve un terremoto en Los Angeles de 6,1
妈的，这很重要！
Shit, it's important!
¡Mierda, es importante!
然后我醒了，我的意思是，实际上是深夜，我因为床的移动而醒了。
And I woke up, I mean, it was early night actually, I woke up because of the movement of the bed.
Y me desperté, o sea, fue la noche madrugada en realidad, me desperté por el movimiento de la cama.
停下来，你醒了，跑到了一个广场上。
Stop, you woke up and ran out to a square.
Pará, te despertaste y saliste corriendo a una plaza.
不，不，没什么，因为，你看到了吗？
No, no, nothing because, did you see?
No, no, nada porque, ¿viste?
当你醒来时...
When you wake up...
Cuando vos te despertás...
没有响起警报或任何东西。
No alarm sounded or anything.
No sonó alarma ni nada.
所以当你醒来的时候，你就醒到一半，你就在那里醒来。
So when you wake up, you wake up halfway, you wake up there.
Entonces cuando te despertás, te despertás medio boleta, te despertás ahí.
我意识到一切都在移动，大约 20 秒后我才注意到遥控器。
I realized that everything was moving and it took me about 20 seconds to notice the remote.
Me di cuenta que se estaba moviendo todo y ahí tardé como 20 segundos en darme cuenta del remoto.
在那里我撞倒了门框，这是他们说需要做的，当我走到门框处时
and there I knocked down the door frame, which is what they say needs to be done, and when I went to the door frame
y ya ahí me mandé abajo el marco de la puerta que es la que dicen que hay que hacer y ya cuando fui al marco de la
而且看不到门框。
And the door frame couldn't be seen.
Y el marco de la puerta no se veía.
是的，在地震中你必须钻到门框下面。
Yes, in the earthquake you had to get under the door frame.
Si, en el terremoto vos te tenías que poner debajo del marco de la puerta.
不，也许我想要一个强大的，必须一路运行，然后它会掉进建筑物里……不，好吧，Flejo，但你可以平静地死去。
No, maybe I want a powerful one that has to be run all the way and it falls into buildings and... No, well, Flejo, but you can die peacefully.
No, igual yo quiero uno potente que haya que correr todo y se cae en los edificios y... No, bueno, Flejo, pero te puedes morir tranquilamente.
这是媒体新闻，这不是一场愚蠢的地震。
This was News in the Media, it was not a stupid earthquake.
Este fue Noticias en los Medios, no fue un temblor boludo.
最近这里震动过一次，智利门多萨的圣胡安也震动过，我记得有一天晚上这里很明显。
Once recently it shook here, it shook in San Juan, Mendoza, Chile and it was noticeable here one night, I remember.
Una vez hace poco acá tembló, que tembló en San Juan, Mendoza, Chile y acá se notó una noche, yo me acuerdo.
电子板。
The electronic boards.
Las placas electrónicas.
一个良好的构造板块。
a good tectonic plate.
una buena placa tectónica.
是的，这很强大。
Yes, that's powerful.
Sí, eso eso es potente.
良好的构造板块。
Good tectonic plate.
Buena placa tectónica.
一个在另一个之上的构造板块上跛行
lame on a tectonic plate one above the other
cojudas en una placa tectónica una arriba de la otra
我真的看过有人在三克隆板中潜水的 TikTok 吗？
Had I seriously seen a TikTok of someone diving in a triclonic plate?
¿En serio te había visto un TikTok de una que buceaba en una placa triclónica?
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
很漂亮，呵呵。
Beautiful, huh.
Hermoso, eh.
但打开那个放大镜的怎么会是TikTok呢？
But how can it be what opens that magnifying glass that what opens is TikTok?
¿Pero cómo puede ser lo que abre esa lupita de que lo que abre es el TikTok?
不，算法很糟糕，嘿。
No, the algorithm is pretty bad, hey.
No, el algoritmo viene bastante mal, che.
我不喜欢 TikTok 上的那个。
I don't like the one on TikTok.
No me gusta el de TikTok.
我正在尝试修改它，以便足球出现。
I'm trying to modify it so that football appears.
Lo estoy tratando de modificar para que me aparezca fútbol.
您当前的算法。
Your current algorithm.
Su algoritmo actual.
不，笑话视频，人们录制的视频，我不知道，发生过的事情，但就像那样，自发的。
No, videos of jokes, videos that people recorded of, I don't know, something that happened, but like that, spontaneous.
No, videos de chistes, videos que grabó la gente de, no sé, algo que pasó, pero así, espontáneo.
我想要一个精心编辑的足球视频，带有一些音乐和一个好故事。
I want a well-edited soccer video with some music, a good story.
Yo quiero video de fútbol bien editado con alguna musiquita, un buen relato.
所以我想纠正它们，但它们没有出现，哇。
So I want to correct them, but they don't appear, wow.
Entonces los quiero como que ir corrigiendo, pero no me aparecen, che.
我用算法，我现在有阿拉伯香水。
I'm with the algorithm, I have the Arabic perfumes now.
Yo estoy con el algoritmo, tengo los perfumes árabes ahora.
抱歉，阿拉伯香水怎么样？
Sorry, what about an Arabic perfume?
Perdón, ¿y un perfume árabe?
香水饮料？
Perfume drink?
¿Bebidillo de perfume?
一篇香水评论，什么让你烦恼？
A perfume review, what bothers you?
Un review de perfume, ¿qué te molesta?
一个给你解释的人。
A guy who explains it to you.
Un tipo que te explica.
弗拉·盖比（Fra Gaby）是一个向你解释他有香水的人。
Fra Gaby is a guy who explains to you that he has a perfume.
Fra Gaby es un tipo que te explica que tiene un perfume.
那男孩叫什么名字？
What's the boy's name?
¿Cómo se llama el muchacho?
来自盖比。
From Gaby.
Fra Gaby.
他向你解释说，这个有檀香香、樱桃香、木香。
He explains to you and says, this has sandalwood notes, cherry notes, wood notes.
Te explica y dice, este tiene notas de sándalo, notas de cereza, notas de madera
一点点绿草，他告诉你，然后他把一切都扔给你......
a little bit of green grass, he tells you, and he throws everything at you...
un poquito de pasto verde, te dice, y te va tirando todo lo que...
这是一个谎言，如果它有那么多好东西，那不是为了很多食物，我意识到这是因为日程安排，因为下午所有的餐馆都会出现。
It's a lie, if it has all that good stuff, it's not for many food. I realized that it's because of the schedule because in the afternoon all the restaurants appear.
mentira si tiene todo eso bueno no para muchas comida igual me di cuenta que es por horario che porque a la tarde noche me aparecen todos restaurantes
于是，分部的姑娘们崩溃了，我然后把它发给了所有的小组。
Thus, the branch girls collapse on me, I then send it to all the groups.
Así, las chicas de branch me colapsan, lo mando después a todos los grupos.
看，我们必须去这里，我们必须去那里。
See, we have to go here, we have to go there.
Viste, tenemos que ir acá, tenemos que ir allá.
你是推荐餐馆的人 是的，是的 也许你永远不会去
You are the one who proposes restaurants Yes, yes Maybe you will never end up going
A vos sos el que propone de restaurantes Sí, sí Igual no terminará yendo nunca
一些一般罗德里格斯穿着 有一些美味的地方 看在上帝的份上乡村俱乐部吃吃吃
some in general rodríguez dress there are some delicious places for God's sake country club to eat eat and eat
alguno en general rodríguez viste hay que rico lugares por dios club de campo para comer comer y comer
可口的。
Delicious.
Delicioso.
但你胃口好，吃两块肉就out了。
But you have a good stomach, eat two meats and you're out.
Pero vos sos buen estomago, come dos carnecitos y ya estas afuera.
如果你在美国整天吃三明治 好吧，因为晚上一切都关门了，但是......
If you ate sandwiches all day in the United States And well, because at night things were closed, but...
Si vos comías sanguchitos todo el día en Estados Unidos Y bueno porque a la noche estaba cerrado las cosas, pero...
对我来说，你不必在那里吃早餐。
For me, you didn't have to have breakfast there.
Para mí, ahí no tenías que desayunar.
不是每个地方都有，拜托。
There wasn't every place, please.
No había cada lugar, por favor.
早午餐女孩是一种现象，然后是那些地方……你还记得坐在这里的 Betular 先生吗？
The brunch girl is a phenomenon, and then the places... Do you remember Mr. Betular sitting here?
La chica de brunch es una fenome, y después los lugares... ¿Vos te acuerdas de estuvo acá sentado el señor Betular?
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
甜甜的东西也多么美味啊。
How delicious sweet things are too.
Que rico también las cosas dulces.
除此之外，我还有一个。
Besides, I have one.
Aparte tengo una.
如果您不介意的话，我们有一位过往的国家队教练的便条。
If it doesn't bother you, we have a note from a passing national team coach.
Si no te jode tenemos una nota de un entrenador de la selección que pasa.
我说，那位教练改变了世界。
And that coach changes the world, I say.
Y ese entrenador cambia el mundo, digo.
所以我认为我们可以为此让路，人们已经在等待了，我知道这些演出什么时候出来，他们将以交错的速度进来，好吧，就是现在。
So I think we can make way for that, people are already waiting and I know when these gigs are going to come out, they are going to come in at a staggered pace and well, it's now.
Así que creo que le podemos dar paso a eso, ya la gente está esperando y sé cuándo van a salir estos bolos, van a entrar a escalón y bueno, es ahora.
让我们听听国家队教练的说法吧，他们留下来学习
Let's listen to the coach of the national team eh and they stay as they left study
vamos a escuchar el entrenador de la selección eh y se quedan como se fue estudio
正如我们所承诺的，我们和阿根廷队教练莱昂内尔·斯卡洛尼先生一起欢迎您的到来。
And as we promised, here we are with the coach of the Argentine team, Mr. Leonel Scaloni, we welcome you.
y como les prometimos acá estamos con el entrenador de la selección argentina el señor Leonel Scaloni le damos la bienvenida
或者他欢迎我们。
Or he welcomes us.
O él nos da la bienvenida a nosotros.
里奥，怎么样？
Leo, how's it going?
Leo, ¿cómo va?
好吧，这更多的是你的而不是我们的，所以我们认为情况正好相反。
Well, this is more yours than ours so we think it's the other way around.
Bien, esto es más tuyo que nuestro entonces nosotros creemos que es al revés
但我们正在照顾办公室，这里的一切都很好，我们拥有应有的所有草坪。
But we are taking care of the office, everything is fine here on the property, we have all the grass as it should be.
Pero te estamos cuidando la oficina, está todo bien acá en el predio, tenemos todo el pasto como tiene que ser.
都割草了。
All cut grass.
Pasto cortadito todo.
不，小心点，我们就在附近，现在我们什么，20、30米远？
No, be careful, we are close by, now we are what, 20, 30 meters away?
No, cuídense que estamos al ladito, ahora estamos a cuánto, ¿20, 30 metros?
是的，有人感觉被监视，我告诉你真相。
Yes, one feels watched, I tell you the truth.
Sí, uno se siente observado, te digo la verdad.
当有人经过时，我们低着头走过。
When one passes by, we walk past with our heads down.
Uno cuando pasa por ahí, pasamos caminando con cabeza gacha.
让我们把我们的窗户...
Let's put the window of our...
Vamos a poner la ventana de nuestra...
我们办公室的房间面向另一侧，面向你的、老师的和守门员教练的，所以很安静。
from our office faces the other side, the one that faces yours, the teacher's and the goalkeeper coach's, so it's quiet.
de nuestra oficina da para el otro lado, la que da para la de ustedes, la del profe y la del entrenador arquero, así queda tranquilo.
好，好。
Good, good.
Bien, bien.
除了老师，老师也来了。
Aside from the teacher, the teacher is coming.
Aparte el profe, el profe viene.
压力少了一点吧？
One less pressure, right?
Una presión menos, ¿no?
这是一支勇敢的教练组，你看到了吗？
It's a brave coaching staff, you see?
Es un cuerpo técnico bravo, ¿viste?
这是一个勇敢的教练组，这个教练组有它的性格。
It is a brave coaching staff, the coaching staff has its characters.
Es un cuerpo técnico bravo, tiene sus personajes el cuerpo técnico.
我们还没有让塞缪尔来，这似乎是不可能完成的任务，利奥。
We still haven't gotten Samuel to come, it's mission impossible, it seems Leo.
todavía no logramos que venga Samuel, es la misión imposible, parece Leo.
现在他要尼科欺骗他并给他打电话，但是……
Now he was telling Nico to trick him and call him, but...
Ahora me decía a Nico que lo engañe y que lo llame, pero...
大头很难骗。
The big head is difficult to fool.
El cabezón es difícil engañarlo.
当他看到我带他去一个不是他栖息地的地方时，他就不来了。
When he sees that I was taking him to a place that is not his habitat, he doesn't come.
Cuando ve que lo llevaba a un lugar que no es su hábitat, no viene.
没关系，没关系，没关系。
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Está bien, está bien, está bien.
他在其他地方的表现更好，但是嘿，我们几乎拥有了一切。
He moves better elsewhere, but hey, we've had almost everything.
Se mueve mejor en otro lado, pero bueno, lo hemos tenido casi todo.
我们有...
We had...
Tuvimos a...
阿马纳，我们从艾马尔先生那里得到了它，我们得到了它......你不能抱怨。
Amana, we had it from Mr. Aymar, we had it... You can't complain.
Amana, lo tuvimos del señor Aymar, lo tuvimos... No te puede quejar.
我们不会抱怨，我们有教练，所以我们首先要利用它，你好吗，面包店家族对我来说是唯一重要的事情吗？
We are not going to complain and we have the coach so we are going to take advantage of it first how are you first how is the bakery family the only thing that matters to me
no nos vamos a quejar y tenemos al entrenador así que lo vamos a aprovechar primero cómo estás primero cómo está la panadería familia que lo único que a mí me importa
这确实是一个让我屈服的话题。
really the topic that subjugates me.
realmente el tema que a mí me subyuga.
你所有的优点，我们必须要求
All your merits, we must ask for a
Todo mérito de ustedes, hay que pedirle ahí un
给科琳娜药店的百分之一。
A percentage to Corina the pill shop.
Un porcentaje a Corina la pastillería.
嗯，我想没关系，我们并没有和她真正谈论过这件事，但是......
Well, I think it's okay, we didn't really talk about it with her, but...
Bueno, creo que está bien, no mucho no tocamos el tema con ella, pero...
我认为他做得很好，有了你给他的宣传，他一定会做得很好。
I think he is doing well, with the publicity you gave him he will surely do well.
Creo que le va bien, con la publicidad que le hicieron ustedes le dé bien seguro.
我们随时在该地产上开设特许经营权
At any time we open a franchise here on the property
en cualquier momento abrimos una franquicia acá en el predio
现在我开始认真了，因为我们在美洲杯之后没有交谈，我们看到你们度过了庆祝活动。
Now I'm getting serious, because we didn't talk after the Copa América, we saw you spend the day of the celebrations.
Ahora sí metiéndome en serio, porque no hablamos después de Copa América, te vimos pasar el día de los festejos.
我们完全覆盖了溪流，它处于庆祝模式，许多也处于家庭模式。
We had the stream completely covered, it was there in celebration mode and many in family mode too.
teníamos el stream completamente copado, estaba ahí en modo celebración y muchos en modo familia también.
我记得当你赢得上届美洲杯时，我对你进行了采访，FA Estudio 甚至不在那儿，它甚至不存在。
I remember when you won the previous Copa América, I did an interview with you, FA Estudio wasn't even there, it didn't even exist.
Me acuerdo cuando ganaste la Copa América anterior, yo te hice una entrevista, ni siquiera estaba FA Estudio, ni siquiera existía.
你告诉我，我很享受标题后的几秒钟，我闭上眼睛，我很享受。
And you told me, I enjoyed the seconds after the title, I closed my eyes, I enjoyed it.
Y vos me dijiste yo disfruté los segundos después del título, cerré los ojos, disfruté.
然后你很享受这段时间，你更享受，你找到了他
and then you enjoyed this time, you enjoyed more, you found him
y después disfrutaste esta vez, disfrutaste más, le encontraste
能够享受头衔或与谁一起享受头衔的秘诀。
the secret to being able to enjoy a title or who you enjoyed it with out there.
el secreto a poder disfrutar de un título o con quién lo disfrutaste por ahí.
是的，就是这样。
Yes that's how it is.
Sí, es así.
事实是，尤其是因为……
The truth is that, especially because...
La verdad que, sobre todo porque...
我们知道这会很艰难，我们在杯赛之前就遇到了很多问题，球员们表现不佳。
We knew it was going to be tough, we started before the Cup with a lot of problems, players who were not doing well.
Sabíamos que iba a ser dura, empezamos ante la Copa con muchísimos problemas, jugadores que no llegaban bien.
正如他们所说，我们公正地到达了。
We arrived justly, as they say.
llegábamos justos, como quien dice.
是的，当比赛结束时，事实是我庆祝得更多。
And then yes, when the game ended, the truth is that I celebrated a lot more.
Y después sí, cuando termino el partido, la verdad que festejé bastante más.
放松，比其他时候兴奋得多，因为我认为
relaxed, much more excited than the other times because I think
relajado, bastante más emocionado que las otras veces porque creo que
这是值得的，这是值得的
it was worth it, it was worth it
valía la pena, valía la pena
经历了这么多痛苦之后，那届杯赛确实值得庆祝。
After suffering so much, that Cup was really to celebrate.
de tanto sufrir esa Copa fue realmente para festejarla.
它也有一个情感成分，安赫尔要离开。
It also had an emotional component, Ángel was leaving.
Tenía un componente emotivo también, se retiraba Ángel.
决赛已经发生了，我们在决赛中所遭受的一切都是因为他们
the final as it had happened, everything we had suffered that final due to the fact that they had
la final como se había dado, todo lo que habíamos sufrido esa final por el hecho de que habían
发生了一些事件，我们被锁在更衣室里将近一个半小时。
There had been incidents, we had been locked up in the locker room for almost an hour and a half.
Había habido incidentes, habíamos estado casi una hora y media en el vestuario encerrado.
不知道发生了什么。
without knowing what had happened.
sin saber qué había pasado.
这很艰难，但也是一种释放。
It was hard and it was a release.
Fue dura y fue un descargo.
真的，非常情绪化。
It was quite emotional, really.
Fue bastante emotivo, la verdad.
而且，即使是玩家也必须...
And besides, even the players have to...
Y aparte, incluso los jugadores tienen que...
与家人交谈，看看他们的表现如何，我说这是一场我想象的就像调味料的决赛
to talk to the family to see how they were doing, I say it was a final that had like a seasoning I imagine
que hablar con la familia que ver cómo estaban digo fue una final que tuvo como un condimento imagino
这不是一场正常的决赛。
It was not a normal final.
No fue una final normal.
不，除此之外，当你看到那个时我会告诉你......
No, apart from that I tell you when you see that...
No, aparte para eso te digo cuando ves que...
有你的家人，有问题，可能会发生一些事情，足球退居次要地位。
There is your family, there are problems and something could happen, football takes a backseat.
está tu familia, hay problemas y que puede pasar algo, el fútbol queda en segundo plano.
我们一直说这很重要，但最终……
We have always said that it is important, but in the end...
siempre hemos dicho que es importante, pero que al final...
还有很多更重要的事情，首先是家庭。
There are much more important things and the first is family.
Hay cosas muchísimo más importantes y la primera es la familia.
而不少球员也很担心，他们甚至在更衣室外寻找家人。
and many players were worried, they were even outside the locker room, looking for family members.
y muchos jugadores estaban preocupados, estaban incluso fuera del vestuario, buscando a los familiares.
我们告诉他们要真正担心自己，然后再考虑足球。
We told them to really worry about them and then think about football.
Nosotros les dijimos que se preocupen realmente por ellos y que después piensen en el fútbol.
除了决赛之外，这是最重要的事情。
Beyond it being a final, it was the most important thing.
más allá de que sea una final, era lo más importante.
哥伦比亚男孩也很......
The Colombian boys were also quite...
Los chicos colombianos también estaban bastante...
冷静一些，我认为有一两个球员遇到了我们遇到的问题
calmer I think there were one or two players with a problem we had
más tranquilo creo que había uno o dos jugadores con algún problema nosotros teníamos
又进行了几次，最终一切都解决了，但也有一些不确定的时刻。
several more and in the end everything was resolved, but they were moments of uncertainty.
varios más y al final todo se solucionó, pero fueron momentos de incertidumbre.
y
你谈到享受它，我想你有人在等着你，很高兴看到你成为冠军。
You talked about enjoying it, I imagine you had people waiting for you and happy to see you champion.
hablaste de disfrutarlo, me imagino que tenía gente que te estaba esperando y feliz de verte campeón.
当爸爸成为冠军后，家里会发生什么？
What happens to the family when dad becomes champion?
¿Qué pasa con la familia cuando papá vuelve campeón?
那个可爱的人的隐私里一定也有什么秘密吧。
There must be something in the privacy of that cute too.
debe haber algo que en la intimidad de ese lindo también.
嗯，我很幸运，他们在卡塔尔，在球场上，他们也在这里，他们是来参加决赛的。
Well, I was lucky that they were there in Qatar, on the court and they were here too, they came for the final.
Bueno, tuve la suerte que en Qatar estuvieron, en la cancha y en esta también estuvieron, vinieron para la final.
能够和他们在一起是一件很了不起的事......
and being able to have been with them is something...
y poder haber estado con ellos es algo...
我认为这是一个人能拥有的最美丽的礼物，能够和你的孩子一起享受，让他们看到。
I think it is the most beautiful gift one can have, to be able to enjoy it with your children, for them to see.
Yo creo que es el regalo más lindo que uno puede tener, poder disfrutar con tus hijos, que ellos vean.
它使人民多么幸福，使一个国家多么幸福。
how happy it makes people, makes a country.
lo feliz que hace la gente, hacer un país.
这就是我所喜欢的，特别是因为我看到他们也很高兴。
And that's what I loved, especially because I saw them happy too.
Y eso es lo que a mí me ha encantado, sobre todo porque yo se los veía felices también.
你带纪念品吗？
Do you bring souvenirs?
¿Llevas suvenir?
他会给你一件T恤吗？他会给你送什么东西吗？他会给你带来纪念品吗？还是他不是一个值得珍惜的好人？
Does he get a t-shirt, does he get you something, does he bring you a souvenir or is he not a good person to treasure?
¿Se consigue alguna camiseta, te consigue algo, te lleva algún recuerdo o no sobe atesorar?
你知道吗，通常有一门课程的效力是最少的……？
Do you know that normally there is a potenic course that has the least...?
¿Vos sabes que normalmente hay curso poténico el que menos...?
纪念品少了，尤其是我们不索要，不……
Souvenirs get less, especially because we don't ask for them, no...
que menos le llegan los souvenirs, sobre todo porque aparte no pedimos, no...
通常当有礼品 T 恤或纪念品时，最后到达的
and normally when there is a gift t-shirt or there is a commemorative, the last ones to arrive
y normalmente cuando hay una camiseta de regalo o hay algún conmemorativo, los últimos que llegan
这是教练组。
It's the coaching staff.
es el cuerpo técnico.
但我对决赛本身没有任何具体的了解。
But I don't have anything specifically about the finals themselves.
pero de las finales en sí en concreto no tengo nada.
事实上，我想我把马球送给了一个总是穿着这件衬衫的男孩。
In fact, I think I gave the polo to a boy who always wore the shirt.
de hecho creo que el polo se lo regalé a un chico que siempre llevaba la camiseta
她很高兴，穿着我的一件衬衫，在决赛中她又穿上了它，我把马球给了她。
Delighted, she was wearing one of my shirts and there in the final she wore it again and I gave her the polo.
encantada, llevaba una camiseta mía y ahí en la final la volvió a llevar y le di el polo.
我不认为我从那场比赛中得到任何东西，但回忆对我来说已经足够了。
And I don't think I have anything from that game, but the memories are enough for me.
y no creo que no tengo nada de ese partido, pero me basta con los recuerdos.
今天有一张照片，很多年前你一无所有。
Today there is a photo, many years before you had nothing.
Hoy hay foto, mucho años antes no tenías nada.
今天有照片，有视频，什么都有，你都可以看到。
Today there is a photo, there is a video, there is everything and you can see it.
Hoy hay foto, hay video, hay de todo y lo puedes ver.
社交网络一千次，那是最好的。
a thousand times social networks, that's the best.
mil veces las redes sociales, eso es lo mejor.
好吧，我现在就开始讲，如果现在有准备，就有
Well, I'll get into it now, if at present there was preparation, there was
bueno me meto ahora si en la actualidad hubo preparación hubo
迈阿密的一个不同方案我想它有一些特别的东西，我问自己的是我爱你。
a different scheme Miami I imagine that it has something special and what I ask myself is what I love you.
un esquema distinto Miami me imagino que tiene todo una cosa especial y yo lo que me pregunto y es lo que te quiero.
瓦伦丁告诉我是的，因为我们之前就讨论过这个问题。
Valentín tells me yes because we were talking about it beforehand.
Valentín me dice que sí porque lo estuvimos hablando en la previa.
当然，迈阿密国际有里奥，他打开了大门，迈阿密国际有大卫·贝克汉姆。
Of course, Inter Miami has Leo, he opens the doors, Inter Miami has David Beckham.
Claro, Inter de Miami está Leo, abre las puertas, Inter de Miami tiene a David Beckham.
我在网上看到了拉科鲁尼亚辉煌体育时代的视频
and I saw a video on the internet of the glorious sporting era of La Coruña
y yo vi en internet un video de la gloriosa época deportivo de la coruña
你和大卫·贝克汉姆之间的交叉
of a cross between you and David Beckham
de un cruce tuyo con David Beckham
呃呃，你们又交叉了。
Uh, uh, you've crossed paths again.
Uh, uh, te lo has vuelto a cruzar.
有谈话，没有谈话，但很辣。
There was talk, there was no talk, but it was spicy.
Se ha charlado, no se ha charlado, pero fue picante.
它发生了并且留下了。
It happened and it stayed.
Pasó y quedó.
我们再次见面，互相打招呼，拍了一张非常漂亮的照片。
We saw each other again, we greeted each other, we took a very nice photo.
Nos volvimos a ver, nos saludamos, sacamos una foto muy gentil.
但这都是我的错。
But that was all my fault.
Pero eso fue todo culpa mía.
都是我的错。
All my fault.
Todo culpa mía.
那场战斗，如果你可以称之为战斗的话，是因为……
That fight, if you can call it a fight, was due to...
Esa pelea, si se puede llamar pelea, fue por propio de la...
由于他们在伯纳乌还剩一分半钟时没有进球而感到愤怒。
from the anger that they had not scored a goal, with a minute and a half left there at the Bernabéu.
de la bronca de que ellos no habían hecho un gol, faltando un minuto y medio ahí en el Bernabéu.
一场非常重要的比赛
A very important match that
Un partido importantísimo que nos
我们在第一场联赛中以一对一的方式与港口作战，他们以二比一击败了我们，没有遗漏任何东西
We fought the first league ports we went one to one, they beat us two to one with nothing missing
nos peleábamos los primeros puertos de liga íbamos uno a uno, nos ganaron dos a uno faltando nada
愤怒的时候，你看看没有愤怒的地方。
of the anger, you look where there is none.
de la bronca, buscas donde no hay.
而且它确实不符合故事本身。
and it really didn't fit the story as it were.
y realmente no venía al cuento como quien dice.
这是一个以他作为球员所取得的成就为标志的时刻。
It was a moment that has been marked by what he generated as a player.
Fue un momento que ha quedado marcado por lo que él generaba como jugador.
20年后的今天，你意识到我错了。
Today, 20 years later, you realize that I was the wrong one.
Hoy, 20 años después, te da cuenta de que el equivocado era yo.
好吧，那很好，但我也必须把皇马也纳入运动队。
Well, that's fine, but I had to put that Real Madrid in the sports one too.
Bueno, pero está bien, pero al deportivo le tenía que meter a ese Real Madrid también.
我必须打得好，但我也必须付出一些努力。
I had to play well, but I also had to put in some effort.
Tenía que jugar bien, pero había que meterle también.
不，我们和他们竞争。
No, we competed with them.
No, competíamos con ellos.
我们甚至赢了。
We have even won.
Incluso hemos ganado.
我是进球者之一，但我没有能力在那支球队中踢球。
I was one of those who scored, I didn't have the quality to play on that team.
Yo era de los que metía, yo no tenía para jugar en ese equipo calidad.
我做了我的工作。
I did my job.
Hacía mi trabajo.
有时是好的，有时是这样的事情发生在我身上。
Sometimes good and sometimes like this happened to me.
A veces bueno y a veces como esto me pasaba.
这就是为什么随着时间的推移你会变得更好。
That's why over time you get better.
Por eso con el tiempo uno va mejorando.
多么勇敢，那些决斗是巨大的。
How brave, those duels were tremendous.
Que bravo, esos duel eran tremendos.
除了跑车之外，Leo 在 Mata Gigante 中间还有那个，这就像一支不舒服的球队......
Aside from the sports car, Leo had that in the middle of Mata Gigante, it was like an uncomfortable team for...
A parte el deportivo, Leo tenía eso en medio de Mata Gigante, era como un equipo incómodo para...
百年纪念胜利了，四次胜利了
that the centenary has won, that has won four times
que le ha ganado el centenario a eso le ha ganado cuatro veces
当时拉科鲁尼亚和瓦伦西亚，由于拉通和巴勃罗在比赛，
At that time, Deportivo and Valencia, since Ratón and Pablo were playing,
En esa época, el Deportivo y el Valencia, desde que jugaban el Ratón y Pablo,
他们甚至参加比赛，有时甚至超过皇家马德里。
They even competed and were above Real Madrid at times.
Incluso disputaban y estaban por encima en algunos momentos de Real Madrid.
巴塞罗那，99年至2005年。
Barcelona, ​​from 99 to 2005.
Barcelona, del año 99 al 2005.
瓦列查赢得了两个联赛冠军，我们赢了一个，我们两次获得亚军。
Vallecha won two leagues, we won one, we were runners-up twice.
El Vallecha ganó dos ligas, nosotros ganamos una, fuimos dos veces subcampeones.
我们在那里。
We were there.
Estábamos ahí.
我什至认为我们正处于胜利的边缘。
I even think we were on the verge of winning.
Incluso creo que nos quedamos a la puerta de poder haber ganado.
冠军联赛，我们已经进入了半决赛，我们也进入了四分之一决赛。
The Champions League, we have reached the semifinal, we have also been in the quarterfinals.
La Champions, hemos llegado al semifinal, hemos quedado en el cuarto de final también.
很遗憾，因为我们有团队。
A shame because we had teams.
Una lástima porque equipos teníamos.
我们缺乏所有球队都需要的运气。
We lacked that dose of luck that all teams need.
Nos faltó esa dosis de suerte que todos los equipos necesitan.
您目前正在观看哪些有关足球的内容？
What are you currently watching about football?
¿Qué están mirando actualmente de fútbol?
那？
That?
¿Qué?
你有没有看到任何你喜欢、你喜欢看、你每周都会重复的球队？
Do you see any team that you like, that you like to watch, that you repeat every week?
¿Ves algún equipo que te guste, que tenés la afición de verlo, que te repetís cada semana?
在你的义务之外。
outside your obligation.
fuera de tu obligación.
或者也许你会说，看，我必须见到这么多球员，事实是我看到了我能看到的一切，仅此而已。
Or maybe you say, look, I have to see so many players that the truth is I see everything I can and that's it.
O tal vez decís, mira, tengo que ver tantos jugadores que la verdad veo todo lo que puedo y ya está.
我没有停下来观察任何一支球队本身。
There is no team per se that I stop to look at.
No hay un equipo en sí que me paro a ver.
我或多或少喜欢它...
I like it more or less...
Me gusta más o menos...
勒沃库森和曼城的踢球哲学......
The philosophy of how Leverkusen, Manchester City play...
La filosofía de cómo juega el Leverkusen, el Manchester City...
他们是我喜欢的球队，他们是你追随的球队。
They are teams that I like, they are teams that you follow.
Son equipos que a mí me gusta, son equipos que uno lo sigue.
有时他可以和我们国家队的球员一起做事。
Sometimes he can do things with our players in the national team.
a veces puede hacer cosas con nuestros jugadores en la selección.
然后是的，然后还有细微差别。
Then yes, then there are the nuances.
Después sí, después están los matices.
我们没有那么多时间来准备一些事情。
We don't have that much time to prepare some things.
Nosotros no tenemos tanto tiempo de preparar algunas cosas.
但我们确实会研究什么可以或多或少地融入我们的游戏理念。
but we do look at what can more or less be assimilated to our idea of ​​the game.
pero sí que miramos y lo que más o menos se pueda asimilar a nuestra idea de juego.
阿根廷可以吗？
Could the Argentine?
¿Pudo el argentino?
某物？
Something?
¿Algo?
当然，当然，我们看阿根廷足球，我们看到了一切。
And of course, of course, we watch Argentine football, we see everything.
Y claro, claro, miramos el fútbol argentino, lo vemos todo.
河床、博卡、贝莱斯都做得很好，土库曼德萨巴竞技我认为做得很好，胡拉坎。
River, Boca, Vélez who are doing very well, Atlético Tucumán de Saba who I think are doing a great job, Huracán.
River, Boca, Vélez que está muy bien, Atlético Tucumán de Saba que creo que está haciendo un gran trabajo, Huracán.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
他们是一支充满战斗力的球队，最重要的是，他们踢得很好。
They are teams that are fighting and above all that play well.
Son equipos que están dando guerra y sobre todo que juegan bien.
贝儿演得很好。
Bele plays well.
Bele juega bien.
你一直做得很好，我认为你走在正确的轨道上。
You have been doing things very well and I think you are on the right track.
te viene haciendo las cosas muy bien y creo que va por buen camino.
我们从逻辑上看待它，因为我们必须关注球员。
And we look at it, logically, because we have to look at the players.
Y lo miramos, lógico, porque tenemos que mirar los jugadores.
当地足球的一部分，有时如果我们真的相信值得的话，他们就会被征召。
of local football and that sometimes they are called up if we really believe it is worth it.
del fútbol local y que a veces son convocados si realmente creemos que vale la pena.
我们缺少的位置上的惩罚。
the penalty in positions that we lacked.
la pena en posiciones que nos daban falta.
狮子座，我谨向您表示对您的任务应有的尊重。
I ask you please, Leo, with all the respect that your task deserves.
Te pido por favor Leo, con todo el respeto que me merece tu tarea.
芝加哥正在为领先而战，请不要给任何人打电话，我的意思是，我们打得很好，我请求你们......我们不会放弃你们中的任何人。
Chicago is fighting for the lead, please let's not call anyone, I mean, we are playing well, I ask you please... We are not going to drop any of you.
Chicago está peleando la punta, por favor no citemos a nadie, o sea, estamos jugando bien, te pido por favor que... No te vamos a caer ninguno.
我们不会放弃你们中的任何一个人。
We're not going to drop any of you.
No te vamos a caer ninguno.
让我们至少坚持到今年年底，因为这种情况每十年就会发生一次，请我们存钱。
Let's hold on until the end of the year at least as this happens once every 10 years, please let's bank.
Aguantemos hasta fin de año por lo menos que esto pasa una vez cada 10 años, por favor banquemos.
我们总是谈论整个团队宇宙及其背后的人。
We always talk a lot about the entire team universe and the people behind it.
Siempre hablamos mucho de todo el universo selección y de la gente que está detrás.
我喜欢厨师、切刀师的故事……
I like the story of a cook, a cutter...
A mí me gusta la historia de cocinero, de cutilero...
迭戈先生的水平如何？
How is Mr. Diego's level?
¿Cómo está el nivel de señor Diego
如果我们不知道，我们要做什么烘焙？
What are we going to do roasts if we don't know?
¿Qué vamos a hacer asados si no sabemos?
我们不知道是否要起飞。
We don't know if we're going to take off or not.
No sabemos si vamos a despegar o no.
我们对气候问题很复杂，我们有点警惕，因为
We are complicated with the climate issue, we are a little alert because the
Estamos complicados con el tema del clima, estamos un poquito alerta porque la
我们还没有遇到任何问题，但事实是一切都非常警惕。
We haven't had any problems yet, but the truth is that everything is very alert.
No hemos tenido problemas todavía, pero la verdad que está todo muy alerta.
我们也无法像往常一样享受典型的烧烤。
and we have not been able to have the typical barbecue that we always do.
y no hemos podido el asado típico que hacemos siempre.
当我们到达酒店时，迭戈会做这件事，当然是周六。
Diego will do it when we get to the property, surely on Saturday.
Lo hará Diego cuando lleguemos al predio, el sábado seguramente.
球员们和 AFA 周围的所有人一起享受了一次愉快的烧烤。
A good barbecue between the players and all the people who surround the AFA.
Un buen asado entre los jugadores y toda la gente que rodea a la AFA.
我们不值得，因为我们仍然在这里度过了相当紧张的几天。
We don't deserve it, because we still spent quite a few stressful days here.
No merecemos, porque pasamos unos días todavía bastante estresantes acá.
因为他们在那儿，他们在旅行，他们没有旅行，我们必须看看他们是否在旅行，我们必须看看航班是哪一天，对吧？
Because they were there, they were traveling, they weren't traveling, we had to see if they were traveling, we had to see what day the flight was, right?
Ya porque estaban, que viajaban, que no viajaban, que ver si viajaban, que ver qué día era el vuelo, ¿no?
他们就在那个里面。
They were in that one.
Estaban en esa.
这。
THIS.
EZT.
我们度过了艰难的日子，这是我们计划旅行时没有想到的。
We spent difficult days and we did not expect it when we planned the trip.
Pasamos días complicados y no esperábamos cuando planificamos el viaje.
到迈阿密，我们考虑的是球员的舒适度，最重要的是......
to Miami, we think about the comfort of the player and above all that...
a Miami, pensamos en la comodidad del jugador y sobre todo que...
从阿根廷到委内瑞拉，会有一些复杂的情况。
It is from Argentina to Venezuela and there are going to be complications.
que es de Argentina para Venezuela y va a haber complicaciones.
好吧，如果我们到达，我们必须在另一个国家中途停留，然后去……
Well, if we arrive, we have to make a stopover in another country and then go to...
bueno, de llegar, tenemos que hacer una escala en otro país para después ir a...
马图林和球员们周二全天都会到达，我们没有时间训练。
Maturín and the players were going to arrive all day Tuesday, we weren't going to have time to train.
a Maturín y los jugadores nos iban a llegar todo el martes, no íbamos a tener tiempo de entrenar.
所以原则上这是最好的，有时事情可能会因为问题而出错。
So in principle this was the best and sometimes things can go wrong due to issues.
Así que en principio lo mejor era esto y a veces las cosas por cuestiones se pueden torcer.
是的，这很复杂。
It was complicated, yes.
Fue complicado, sí.
你们相处得很好。
Planes you get along well.
Aviones te llevas bien.
对于飞机主题，您已经习惯了。
With the airplane theme you are already used to it.
Con tema avión ya estás acostumbrado.
不，不，我总是相处得很糟糕，一点一点地。
No, no, I always got along badly, little by little it does.
No, no, siempre me lleve mal, poco a poco lo hace.
你咀嚼它，最后你会意识到......
You chew it and you realize that in the end...
La vas masticando y te vas dando cuenta que al final...
如果最终你不得不旅行，你就会受苦。
If in the end you had to travel, you suffered.
Si al final tenías que viajar, se sufría.
他受了很多苦，他是受苦最深的人之一，随着时间的推移
He suffered a lot, he was one of those who suffered the most and over time
lo sufría bastante, era uno de los que más sufría y con el tiempo
你失去了恐惧，他们向你解释，有时你会……
you lose that fear, they explain it to you, sometimes you go...
vas perdiendo ese miedo, te van explicando, a veces vas...
我们乘坐包机时我已经进过机舱了。
I have gone in the cabin when we went on a charter flight.
He ido en cabina cuando íbamos a un vuelo charter.
他们向你解释并告诉你飞机为何飞行，但是......
and they explain to you and they tell you why the plane flies, but...
y te van explicando y te van diciendo como por qué vuela el avión, pero...
最后，这么多的飞行时间你是被迫的，因为我们住在飞机上方相当高的地方。
In the end, with so many flight hours you are forced because we live quite high above the planes.
Al final, con tanta hora de vuelo estás obligado porque vivimos bastante arriba de los aviones.
换句话说，您进行了前往机舱并发现所有这些视频都很好的练习，试图了解它的内容。
In other words, you did the exercise of going to the cabin and finding out that all this video is good, trying to see what the thing is about.
o sea hiciste el ejercicio de ir a cabina y averiguar que todo este video es bueno tratar como de ver de que va la cosa
是的，当我们在运动中飞行时。
Yes, when we flew in sport.
Sí, cuando volábamos en el deporte.
我们会在每个年级把你踢出去，因为当然，我们每三天就打一场比赛。
that we were going to kick you out for every grade because, of course, we played every three days.
que íbamos a echarte para todo grado porque, claro, jugábamos cada tres días.
我们总是与同一家公司一起飞行，几乎总是飞行员、机组人员都是相同的，而且我们总是包机。
We always flew with the same company and almost always the pilots, the crew were the same and we always went by charter.
Volábamos siempre con la misma compañía y casi siempre los pilotos, la tripulación era la misma y siempre iba en charter.
我在机舱里起飞了，抱歉，我和他们一起起飞了。
I took off in the cabin, sorry, I took off with them.
despegaba en cabina perdón, despegaba con ellos.
起飞后，我和我的同伴一起出发，然后当我必须降落时，我又回来了。
After takeoff I went with my companions and then when I had to land I returned.
después del despegue me iba con los compañeros y después cuando había que aterrizar volvía.
我已经在机舱内完成了一百多次飞行。
I have done more than a hundred and something flights in the cabin.
He hecho más de ciento y pico vuelos en cabina.
这确实帮助我理解了很多事情，为什么它会移动以及为什么......
and that really helped me understand many things, why it moved and why...
y eso sí que me ayudó a entender muchísimas cosas, por qué se movía y por qué...
许多事情帮助我摆脱了这种恐惧。
many things that have helped me get rid of that fear.
muchas cosas que me ha ayudado a sacarme ese miedo.
瓦伦丁科洛尼亚的阿尔维多机场，我向您提供这些信息，以便您可以处理不......
Alvedo Airport in Colonia, Valentín, I give you that information so that you can handle data that does not...
Aeropuerto Alvedo en la Colonia, Valentín, te doy ese dato para que maneje datos que no...
不是每个人都会开车，利奥。
Not everyone drives, Leo.
No cualquiera maneja, Leo.
不是每个人都会开车。
Not everyone drives.
No cualquiera maneja.
它是最危险的之一，但那里的情况有点糟糕。
It is one of the most dangerous, but it is in a bit of a situation there.
Es uno de los más peligrosos, pero sí que está en una situación un poco ahí.
你看到了山脉，你看到了短道......
you saw the mountains, you saw short track...
viste la montaña, viste pista corta...
好吧，当我们旅行时，我们有时会降落在圣地亚哥德孔波斯特拉，因为机场关闭。
Well, when we came on a trip we sometimes landed in Santiago de Compostela because the airport closed.
Bueno, cuando veníamos de viaje a veces aterrizábamos en Santiago de Compostela porque el aeropuerto cerraba.
迷雾很大，我有很多故事要讲，最后你就摆脱了恐惧，就这样走了。
a lot of fog, I have a lot of stories to tell and in the end you get rid of the fear and go like that.
mucha niebla, tengo para contar un montón de historias y al final el miedo te lo sacas y vas así.
殖民地中有如此多的雾，这就是为什么选择......
of so much fog in the colony that is why the choice of...
de tanta niebla en la colonia es por eso la elección de...
生命所在的地方，就和这么多年的太阳有关。
of the place of life, it has to do with the sun, of so many years.
del lugar de vida, tiene que ver con el sol, de tantos años.
你要去那里吗？
Are you going there?
¿Va por ahí?
不，真的，拉科鲁尼亚你最终已经习惯了。
No, really, La Coruña you ended up getting used to it.
No, de verdad que la coruña te terminaste acostumbrando.
直到最后我都想念天气，不热，不是很热。
and until the end I miss the weather, it is not hot, it is not very hot.
y hasta la terminada extrañando el clima, no es caluroso, no hace mucho calor.
天气很冷，所以是灰色的，你会习惯的，事实是，这是一个......
It is very cold, so it is gray and you get used to it, the truth is that it is a place that...
es de hacer muchísimo frío, entonces sí que es gris y te termina acostumbrando, la verdad que yo es un sitio que...
对我来说，这里就像我的第二个家，他们对我们很好，而且到处都是阿根廷人。
For me it is like my second home, they have treated us wonderfully and it is full of Argentinians.
Para mí es como mi segunda casa, nos han tratado de maravilla y está lleno de argentinos.
真正的阿根廷人去了加利西亚，反之亦然，他们对我们很好。
The real Argentines have gone to Galicia and vice versa and treat us wonderfully.
Los verdaderos argentinos han ido a Galicia y viceversa y nos tratan de maravilla.
您沉迷于章鱼或海鲜，对吧？
You indulged in octopus or seafood, right?
¿Te entregabas al pulpo o marisco no?
我在那里的那些年里，这并没有引起人们的注意，我总是遇到问题，他们邀请我去俱乐部，俱乐部就是法律。
It didn't ring a bell during the years I was there, I always had the problem, they invited me to the clubs, that the clubs are the law.
No sonó de los años que estuve ahí, siempre tenía el problema, me invitaban a las peñas, que las peñas son la ley.
仓库里的那些将是小镇。
The ones in the depo were going to be the little towns.
Las del depo iban a ser los pueblitos.
Peña de Arousa，我们去了阿罗萨，他们准备了......
Peña de Arousa, we went to Arousa and they prepared the...
Peña de Arousa, íbamos a Arousa y te preparaban el...
加利西亚式章鱼、zamburinha、龙虾……
The Galician-style octopus, the zamburinha, the lobster...
El pulpo a la gallega, la zamburinha, la langosta...
但不，我不喜欢它。
But no, I don't like it.
Pero no, no me gusta.
就像一块肉，因为除了到达的小牛肉之外，它也是波赫纳。
Like a piece of meat, because apart from the veal that arrives, it is bohena too.
Como un pedazo de carne, porque aparte de la ternera que llega, de bohena también.
然后这件事发生在我身上，凭借所有良好的倾向，加利西亚海鲜，
Then that happened to me, that with all good predisposition, Galician seafood,
Entonces me pasaba eso, que yo con toda buena predisposición, el marisco gallego,
我想他们说这是世界上最好的，但我没有吃。
The best in the world, I think they say, and I didn't eat it.
del mejor del mundo, creo que dicen y yo no lo comía.
但令人高兴的是，是的，事实是章鱼很好吃，但不……
but it is a delight, yes, the truth is that the octopus is delicious, but no...
pero es una delicia, sí, la verdad que el pulpo es rico, pero no...
晚餐我没能吃完，说实话，我更喜欢一块肉。
I couldn't finish closing for dinner, I preferred a piece of meat, to be honest.
no me terminaba de cerrar para una cena prefería un pedazo de carne, la verdad.
我在那里玩，我赢得了竞标，游戏在那里赢得了竞标，死，死。
There I played, I won the bid, there the game won the bid, to die, to die.
Ahí jugaba, ganaba pujato, ahí ganaba pujato el juego, a morir, a morir.
加利西亚牛肉很好，要小心它的水平。
The Galician beef is good, be careful it is at those levels.
La ternera gallega es buena, cuidado que está en esos niveles.
肉，尤其是切法，是不同的。
The meat, the cut above all, is different.
La carne, el corte sobre todo es diferente.
但饱满的小牛那里有很多绿色，牛吃得很好。
But the full calf has a lot of green there, the cow eats well.
pero la ternera llena ahí tiene mucho verde, la vaca come bien.
教练组的烤架是否完好或者是否有污渍？
Are there good grills on the coaching staff or are they stained?
En el cuerpo técnico hay buenos asadores o se manca?
不，不，有件事要做，我上次告诉过你，做这件事的老师......
No, well no, there is something to do, I told you the other time, the teacher who does the...
No, bueno no, hay que hace, que la otra vez te lo dije, el profesor que hace el...
烤好了，但是……
The roast is done, but...
Se le hace el asado, pero...
他的水平不是很好，但是他做得太多了，因为剩下的我们等着他完成。
He doesn't have a good level, but he does too much, because the rest we are waiting for him to finish.
No tiene buen nivel, pero demasiado que hace, porque lo demás estamos esperando que termine.
吃，就是它太好了，我们有它的责备。
to eat, that is, it is too good, we have it to reproach.
para comer, o sea que es demasiado bien, lo tenemos como para reprochar.
它来了，它来了。
It comes there, it comes there.
Viene ahí, viene ahí.
好吧，Leo，现在进入...
Well Leo, now getting into the...
Bueno Leo, ya metiéndome un poquito a la...
三四题严谨又运动一点。
the three four questions of rigor and a little more sporty.
las tres cuatro preguntas de rigor ya un poco más deportiva.
我们怎样才能把火重新点燃呢？
How do we light the fire back?
¿Cómo prendemos el fuego de vuelta?
你已经习惯了完成并重新生火这件事，你看这一定是最困难的事情。
You already got used to this thing of finishing and lighting the fire again, you saw that it must be the most difficult thing there is.
ya te acostumbraste a esto de terminar y prender el fuego de vuelta viste que debe ser de lo más difícil que hay
我的意思是，显然有一群球员再次习惯了这一点，但这又是一个挑战，说，嘿，好吧，让我们回去吧。
I mean, obviously having a group of players who are used to that again, but it's a challenge again to say, hey, well, let's go back.
Digo, obviamente tener un grupo de jugadores que están recontra acostumbrados a eso, pero es un reto otra vez decir, che, bueno, vamos de vuelta.
我想我以前也说过，最后他们习惯了竞争，当他们出去玩的时候……
I think I said it the other time, in the end they are used to competing and when they go out to play...
Yo creo que lo dije la otra vez, al final ellos están acostumbrados a competir y cuando salen a jugar...
他们穿着阿根廷球衣参加比赛。
With the Argentina shirt, they compete.
con la camiseta de Argentina, compiten.
很多事情你不需要提醒他。
You don't need to remind him of many things.
No hace falta recordarle muchas cosas.
如果你发现某些事情失败了，你就会说出来并尝试。
And if you see that something is failing, you say it and you try.
Y si se ve que algo está fallando, se dice y se intenta.
他们试图改变，但他们的DNA中已经存在着竞争。
They try to change, but they already have competition inside, in their DNA.
Se intenta cambiar, pero llevan ya la competición adentro, en su ADN.
这更容易，它让一切变得更容易。
and that is easier, it makes everything much easier.
y eso es más fácil, hace todo mucho más fácil.
之后你可能会赢也可能不会，但他们会继续有想要竞争的欲望。
Afterwards you can win or not, but they will continue to have that desire to want to compete.
Después se puede ganar o no, pero esa gana de querer competir la van a seguir teniendo.
有这样的团队
there is something like that the team
hay algo como que el equipo
战斗的过程，适应即将发生的事情，打得好，当你打得不好时，也要承担起竞争的任务。
of the battle, of adapting to what comes at hand, playing well and when you can't play well, being up to the task of being competitive as well.
de la batalla, de acomodarse a lo que toque jugando bien y cuando no se puede jugar bien estando a la altura de lo competitivo también.
这就是所要求的。
That is what is requested.
Es eso de lo que se pide.
你不能强迫球员或球队获胜。
You cannot force a player or a team to win.
A un jugador o a un equipo no le puede obligar a ganar.
因为对手在比赛，所以可能会发生很多事情。
Because the opponent plays, many things can happen.
porque el rival juega, pueden pasar muchas cosas.
但是，是的，要竞争，要尽力而为。
But yes, to compete, to give your best.
Pero sí, a competir, a dar el máximo.
为了他的伙伴，为了他的国家。
for his partner, for his country.
por su compañero, por su país.
简而言之，就是最大限度地奉献自己，这就是他们每次来都会做的事情。
In short, to give themselves to the maximum and that is what they do every time they come.
En definitiva, a brindarse al máximo y eso es lo que hacen cada vez que vienen.
以及他们在每场比赛中所表现出的超越结果的内容。
and what they demonstrate in each match, beyond the result.
y lo que demuestran en cada partido, más allá del resultado.
我在多大程度上不会提及它是好是坏？
How much am I not going to refer to whether it is good, whether it is bad?
¿Cuánto no me voy a remitir a si está bien, si está malo?
对德鲁的制裁对你个人造成了多大的影响？
How much did the sanction against Draw screw you up personally?
¿Cuánto te jodió lo personal en la sanción a Dibu?
你有没有看到你打开手机或者有人告诉你或者有人告诉你？
Did you see that you open the phone or someone tells you or someone tells you?
¿Viste que abrís o el teléfono o alguien te dice o alguien te manda?
或者算一下官方的通讯，你会发现此刻就像
or calculate the official communication, you find out at the moment it's like
o calcula la comunicación oficial, te enteras en el momento es como
妓女，对吧？
Whore, right?
Puta, ¿no?
我的意思是...是的，当然...不，拧迪布，卡蒂斯...
I mean... Yes, of course... No, screw Dibu, Cutis...
Digo... Sí, claro que... No, jodela de Dibu, la de Cutis...
尤其是因为他们不处于现场比赛的条件下。
Especially because they were not in the conditions of an on-field match.
Sobre todo porque no fueron en condiciones de un partido dentro de la cancha.
库蒂在比赛中也被砍掉了手柄。
Cuti also had his handle taken off for the match.
El Cuti también le sacaron la manilla por el partido.
不，它不痛，而且不好。
No, it doesn't hurt and it's not good.
No, no duele y no está bueno.
我们已经做到了。
And we already did it.
Y ya se lo hicimos.
了解这个群体，我认为这很重要。
Know the group, which I think is important.
Saber el grupo, que creo que es importante.
如果一个人必须受到惩罚，那应该是因为一些真正值得的事情，我不知道。
If one has to be punished, it should be for something that was really worth it, I don't know.
que si uno tiene que ser sancionado que sea por algo que realmente valió la pena, no sé.
在游戏中做出有价值的表现。
for making a worthwhile performance in the game.
por hacer un que valía la pena en el partido.
但是抗议和所有这些，我认为我们必须......
But protests and all that, I think we have to...
pero protestas y todo eso, creo que tenemos que...
改进它，埃米利亚诺是第一个认识到它的人。
improve it and Emiliano was the first to recognize it.
mejorarlo y Emiliano fue el primero en reconocerlo.
知道如何识别它很重要，对吧？
It's important that you know how to recognize it, right?
Es importante que lo sepa reconocer, ¿no?
当然，除了一个一直是该过程的旗舰的玩家之外，当然，我说......
Of course, in addition to a player who has been a flagship of the process and who, of course, I say...
Claro, además de un jugador que ha sido un insignia del proceso y que, claro, digo...
这不是正常的缺席，而且门将是一个平时不出来的家伙。
It is not a normal absence, plus the goalkeeper is a guy who doesn't usually come out.
No es una ausencia normal, además el arquero es un tipo que no suele salir.
人们甚至希望守门员不要出来
one even hopes that the goalkeeper doesn't come out
incluso uno espera que el arquero no salga
不，当然，当然，我们的守门员是……
No, of course, of course, the goalkeeper for us is...
No, claro, claro, el arquero para nosotros es...
我要告诉你什么？
What am I going to tell you?
¿Qué te voy a contar?
他是一个重要的人物。
He is an important figure.
Es una figura importante.
在体育层面，而且在团体层面。
at a sporting level, but also at a group level.
a nivel deportivo, sino que también a nivel grupal.
他是一个为我们做出很多贡献的男孩。
He is a boy who contributes a lot to us.
Es un chico que nos aporta mucho.
好吧，在这种情况下，好吧，无论谁上场，都会全力以赴，我们知道这是事实，而且他们是凭借自己的优点来到这里的。
Well, in this case, well, whoever gets to play is going to give their all, which we know is true and that they are here on their own merits.
Bueno, en este caso, bueno, el que le toque jugar va a dar el máximo, que sabemos que es así y que está acá por méritos propios.
并利用这个机会。
and take advantage of that opportunity.
y que aproveche esa oportunidad.
狮子座，现在要结束并到达终点，显然希望你能在这方面让人们看到
Leo, now to close and reach the end and obviously wishing you in this that people are going to see
Leo, ya para ir cerrando y llegando al final y obviamente deseándote en esto que la gente va a ver
当我计算你的时候，我让你在飞行中或者你已经在飞行中，祝你旅途愉快。
When I calculate you, I made you in flight or you have been in flight, wishing you a good trip.
cuando calculo vos te hice en vuelo o hayas estado en vuelo, deseándote buen viaje.
你想对粉丝说什么...我的意思是，让我们看看，旅程已经再次开始了。
What do you say to the fan in this... I mean, let's see, the trip has already started again.
¿Qué le decís al hincha en este... digo, a ver, ya arrancó de nuevo el viaje.
两场比赛已经打完了，但对于我们这里没有发言的人来说
Two games have already been played but for us who have not spoken here
ya se jugaron dos partidos pero para nosotros que no hemos hablado aquí
我们有你，我们很享受你，在某种程度上，我们问你。
and we have you and we enjoy you, in some way, we ask you.
y te tenemos y te disfrutamos, de alguna manera, te lo preguntamos.
对于杯赛结束后开始的新旅程，您有什么想说的吗？
What do you tell people on this new journey that starts after the Cup?
¿Qué se le dice a la gente en este nuevo viaje que arranca después de la Copa?
同样的，他们一如既往地继续支持球队。
The same thing, that they continue to support the team as they have always done.
Lo mismo, que sigan apoyando a la selección como han hecho siempre.
事实上，你不能告诉粉丝任何其他事情。
The truth is that you cannot tell the fan anything else.
La verdad que al hincha no se le puede decir otra cosa.
对于阿根廷球迷来说，当他为国家队效力时，他就会把自己的俱乐部抛在一边。
The Argentine fan, when he plays for the national team, leaves his club aside.
Al hincha argentino, cuando juega en la selección, deja de lado su club.
这个选择对它有好处
and this selection has been good for it
y esta selección bueno ha sido para ello
这是我们所经历的所有糟糕事情中的一点空气。
It was a little bit of air within all the bad things we were going through.
Era un poco de aire dentro de todo lo mal que le estábamos pasando.
他们继续做出贡献很重要，因为我们感受到了他们的温暖。
It is important that they continue contributing because we feel their warmth.
Es importante que sigan aportando porque nosotros sentimos el calor de ellos.
我们感受到支持，我们感受到鼓励，我们喜欢它，玩家喜欢这些人
We feel the support, we feel the encouragement, we love it, the players love that people
Sentimos el apoyo, sentimos el aliento, nos encanta, a los jugadores les encanta que la gente
我想要它们。
I want them.
los quiera.
无论结果如何，我希望这种交流永远不会结束。
This is a communion that I hope never ends, regardless of the results.
Esto es una comunión que espero no termine nunca, más allá de los resultados.
总是。
Always.
Siempre.
就必须是这样，无论谁执掌国家队，无论谁作为球员，我认为都必须永远这样。
It will have to be like this, whoever is in charge of the national team, whoever is there as a player, I think that has to be like this forever.
Tendrá que ser así, esté quien esté al comando de la selección, esté quien esté como jugador, creo que eso tiene que ser así para siempre.
看到美丽或接近布拉沃的成功真是太棒了，因为
what a bravo to see see to see the beauty or the success close to bravo because as
que bravo ver ver ver lo lo lindo o el éxito de cerca de bravo porque como
能够提及它，但这里的孩子们的脸令人难以置信，这是一个黄金时代，我说
to be able to mention it, but the faces of the children in this one are incredible, it is a golden era, I say
para poder mencionarla, pero es increíble las caras de los nenes en esta, es una era dorada, digo
这不正常。
It's not normal.
No es normal.
您还可以调整大小并享受它。
And you can also size and enjoy it.
Y también puede dimensionar y disfrutarlo.
这真的很重要。
It's really important.
Es re importante.
这很好，很好，我希望它可以作为一个例子，特别是对于......
It's good, it's good and I hope it serves as an example, especially for...
Está bueno, está bueno y espero que sirva como ejemplo, sobre todo para...
最后的那些人，那些要带我们出去的人是来自……的人。
The guys at the end, the ones who are going to take us out are the guys from...
Los chicos de final, los que nos van a sacar son los chicos de...
他们将成为榜样，我希望他们效仿这一点，这就是为什么好的榜样总是很重要的。
and they are the ones who are going to be examples and I hope they copy this, that is why good examples are always important.
y los que van a ser ejemplos son ellos y ojalá se copien de esto, por eso siempre es importante los buenos ejemplos.
如果你犯了错误，要承认它，并指出它是不对的。
and if you ever make a mistake, recognize it, say it's not right.
y si alguna vez se comete un error reconocerlo, decir que no está bien.
虽然什么也没发生，但他道歉了，仅此而已。
Although nothing happens, he apologizes and that's it.
Aunque no pasa nada, se pide perdón y punto.
我认为这才是重要的，也是这一代人留下的超越游戏的遗产。
I think that is what is important and the legacy beyond the titles that this generation is leaving.
Creo que es lo importante y el legado más allá de los títulos que está dejando esta generación.
好吧，狮子座，我们会释放你。
Well Leo, we are going to free you.
Bueno Leo, te vamos a liberar.
我们始终感谢您为 AFA Studio 带来的改变。
We always thank you for the difference you have with AFA Studio.
Te agradecemos siempre por la diferencia que tenés con AFA Studio.
为了氛围，为了银行，什么也没有。
for the vibe, for the bank and nothing.
por la onda, por la banca y nada.
我们只能给您提供意大利面，但是嘿，我们来了。
We can't give you more than a pastafrona, but hey, here we are.
Nosotros más que una pastafrona no te podemos dar, pero bueno, acá estamos.
不，没关系。
No, it's okay.
No, está bien.
别再给我带糖果了，知道吗？
Don't bring me more candy, you know what?
No me traiga más dulce, ¿sabes qué?
好吧，伙计们，我给你们一个大大的拥抱，我们想要匹配 Leo 的体格，你们非常好。
Well guys, I send you a big hug. We want to match Leo's physique, you are very well.
Bueno chicos, les mando un fuerte abrazo Queremos emparejar el físico Leo, estás muy bien
我们想带你到这一边吗？
Do we want to bring you to this side?
¿Queremos traerte para este lado?
是的，如果我不做运动，你知道我会怎样吗？
Yes, if I don't do sports, do you know how I would be?
Sí, si no hago deporte, ¿sabés cómo estaría?
谢天谢地，自行车在那里，因为如果没有，它会更坚固。
Thank goodness the bike is there, because if not, it would be much stronger.
Menos mal que está la bici, porque si no, estaría bastante más fuerte.
Factudio 缺少老师是问题所在。
That Factudio is missing a teacher is the problem.
que le falta un profe a Factudio, es el problema.
Factudio 必须是他自己的老师之一，因为我们都练习得很差。
Factudio has to be one of his own teachers because we are all practicing poorly.
Factudio tiene que ser uno de sus propios profes porque estamos todos mal practicando.
在有绿色和田野的地方奔跑。
Run around where you have the green and the fields.
Hagan a correr por ahí que tienen el verde y las canchas.
让他们跑。
Make them run.
Hagan a correr.
拥抱，利奥。
Hugs, Leo.
Abrazo, Leo.
感谢一切。
Thanks for everything.
Gracias por todo.
多谢。
Thanks a lot.
Muchísimas gracias.
一个地方。
A place.
Un placer.
一个拥抱。
A hug.
Un abrazo.
向你们俩问好。
Greetings to both of you.
Saludos a los dos.
超。
Chao.
一个拥抱。
A hug.
Un abrazo.
祝你旅途愉快。
Have a good trip.
Buen viaje.
莱昂内尔·斯卡罗尼先生，如果可以的话，请给我总体计划，我们就来这里。
Mr. Leonel Scaloni, if you can, give me the general plan and we'll come here.
El señor Leonel Scaloni, si podés dame el plano general y ya nos venimos para acá.
嗯，还有莱昂内尔·斯卡洛尼先生，是吗？
Well, and there is Mr. Leonel Scaloni, eh?
Bueno, y ahí está el señor Leonel Scaloni, ¿eh?
很好，是吧？
Very good, huh?
Muy bien, ¿eh?
非常好。
Very good.
Muy bien.
看来晚饭前。
Before dinner, it seems.
Antes de cenar, parece.
没什么了不起的，被拍了，多少钱？
nothing spectacular, it was taken, how much was it?
nada espectacular, se tomó, ¿cuánto fue?
我不知道，很长很长。
I don't know, long, long.
No sé, largo, largo.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
再说了，你也不总是逼他，你也不总是逼他。
Besides, you don't always push him, you don't always push him.
Aparte no le arremas siempre, no le arremas siempre.
确切地。
Exactly.
Exactamente.
他走过去站在那里说，听我说，他们会问我这个。
He goes and stands there and says, listen to me, they are going to ask me this.
Se va y se pone ahí y dice, escúchame esto me van a preguntar.
和帕塔弗罗拉，和我的妹妹，拉科鲁尼亚……
with the patafrola, with my sister, la coruña...
con la patafrola, con mi hermana, la coruña...
也许我不知道，因为我不知道这家伙是否很习惯被问到通常的 4 或 5 条新闻。
Maybe I don't know because I don't know if it could be that the guy is very used to being asked the usual 4 or 5 news items.
igual yo no sé porque yo no sé si será que el tipo está muy acostumbrado que le pregunten las 4 o 5 noticias de siempre
你必须把它拿出来一点。
and you have to take it out a little.
y hay que sacarlo un poquito.
昨天发生的事，有人受伤，龙卷风。
What happened yesterday, someone injured, the tornado.
Lo que pasó ayer, algún lesionado, el tornado.
龙卷风，凶猛的龙卷风。
The tornado, the fierce tornado.
El tornado, el tornado bravo.
掉进飞机里？
Falling into airplanes?
¿Cadas a los aviones?
不，不要指望它。
No, don't bank on it.
No, no te la bancas.
不，我喜欢飞翔。
No, I like to fly.
No, me gusta volar.
你喜欢飞行吗？
Do you like to fly?
¿Te gusta volar?
是的，我喜欢飞翔。
Yes, I like to fly.
Sí, me gusta volar.
我喜欢，是的，是的，是的。
I like it, yes, yes, yes.
Me gusta, sí, sí, sí.
但除了你之外，你是一个敢于上战场的家伙。
But apart from you, you are a daring guy who has no problem going into battle.
Pero aparte vos sos un tipo osado que no tiene problema de ir a la batalla.
你认为事情总会有好的结局吗？
Do you think it will always end well?
¿Crees que va a terminar bien siempre?
啊，但我宁愿骑摩托车也不愿坐飞机。
Ah, but I'd rather go on a motorcycle than on a plane.
Ah, pero me daría más cosa ir en moto que en avión
从统计上来看还是非常不错的
Still statistically it is very good
igual estadísticamente está muy bien
这是完全理性的，对吧？
It's completely rational, huh?
Es completamente racional, ¿eh?
碰巧有人摔倒的问题……我们有很多。
It happens that the issue of when one falls... We have a lot.
Pasa que el tema de cuando cae uno... Tenemos un montón.
然后平均值就停在这里，但是......
The average then stops here, but...
El promedio después se va aquí parando, pero...
他一定很不幸。
He must be very unlucky.
Tiene que tener mucha mala suerte.
如果轮到你了，那就轮到你了。
If it's your turn, it's your turn.
Si te toca, te toca.
他说这是世界上最安全的事情。
He says it's the safest thing in the world.
Dice que es lo más seguro del mundo.
好吧，我要写一篇社论，但是飞机工业有多糟糕。
Well, I'm going to make an editorial, but how bad the airplane industry is.
Bueno, voy a hacer una editorial, pero qué mala es la industria de los aviones.
我说，这有多糟糕。
How bad it is, I say.
Qué mala es, digo.
他们让飞机坠落，但其余的事情......
They make planes go down, but the rest of the things...
Ellos hacen que los aviones se caigan, pero el resto de cosas...
食物很糟糕，座位不舒服，一切都很糟糕。
The food is bad, the seat is uncomfortable, everything is bad.
La comida es mala, el asiento es incómodo, todo es malo.
但听我说一件事，机场，我喜欢机场。
But listen to me one thing, airport, I love airport.
Pero escuchame una cosa, aeropuerto, a mí me encanta aeropuerto.
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
我很模糊。
I'm blurry.
Estoy borroso.
我喜欢机场的那一刻。
I like the airport moment.
Me gusta el momento aeropuerto.
我不喜欢。
I don't like.
No, me gusta.
你提前到达，然后拿出你的电脑，开始在那里做一些事情。
You arrive early, then you take out your computer, you start doing a couple of things there.
Llegas temprano, después sacas la compu, pones a hacer un par de cosas ahí.
你把电脑拿出来吗？
Do you take out the computer?
¿Sacas la compu?
你从哪里得到电脑？
Where do you get the computer?
¿Dónde sacas la compu?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
星巴克。
Starbucks.
当然，有时会有一个小地方，比如……有一张桌子，一个插头，你可以在那里呆一会儿。
Of course, sometimes there is a little place like... with a table, a plug, you stay there for a little while.
Claro, a veces hay lugarcito como... con mesita, enchufe, estás un ratito ahí.
我喜欢这里，我喜欢机场。
I like it, I like the airport.
Me gusta, a mí me gusta el aeropuerto.
伟大的时刻。
great moment.
gran momento.
Hervérele，你有卡巴拉斯。
Hervérele, you have cabalas.
Hervérele, usted tiene cabalas.
你没有阴谋集团吗？
Don't you have a cabal?
¿No tiene una cábala?
不。
No.
他没有阴谋集团。
He doesn't have a cabal.
No tiene una cábala.
说吧，是的，是的。
Put it, yes, yes.
Ponele, sí, sí.
¡呃？
¿Eh?
对于邪恶的人来说，是的。
With the evil one, yes.
Con el malevo, sí.
那么你有什么类型的头发？
So what type of hair do you have?
¿Así qué tipo de cabela tiene?
不，我们在热身之前吃的东西
No, something we eat before we warm up
No, algo que comemos antes en la entrada en calor
啊，它有……但我可以告诉你，那么……好吧，我们吃……不，它给了我一个甜峰，一个带有甜峰的乡村 aluvante。
Ah, it has... But I can tell you, that then... Well, we eat... No, it gives me a sweet peak, a country aluvante with sweet peaks.
Ah, tiene... Pero la puedo contar, que entonces... Bueno, comemos... No, me da pico dulce, un alluvante de campo con los picos dulces.
哦，还有你……这就像糖果仪式。
Oh, and you... It's like the candy ceremony.
Ah, y te... Es como la ceremonia de los caramelos.
那个……是的，是的，是的。
The... Yes, yes, yes.
La... Sí, sí, sí.
事实上，那是什么时候？
And in fact, when was it?
Y de hecho, ¿cuándo fue?
最后一个……你来过的那个，你还记得吗？
The last one... the one you came to, do you remember?
El último... al que veniste vos, te acordás?
来自……纽厄尔的他们忘了让我热身
From... with Newell's They forgot to warm me up
De... con Newell's Se olvidó darme la entrada en calor
中场休息时他把球传给了我
and at halftime he gave it to me
y en el entretiempo me lo dio
好吧，最终成功了。
And well, it ended up working out.
Y bueno, termino resultando.
好，好，有效。
Good, good, it works.
Bien, bien, funciona.
但是，是的，是的，是的，总是，一两个甜蜜的峰值，他们在出去热身之前在更衣室里给了我，然后我在热身期间吃了它。
But yes, yes, yes, always, one or two sweet peaks, they give it to me in the locker room before they go out for a warm-up and then I eat it during the warm-up.
Pero sí, sí, sí, siempre, uno o dos picos dulces, me lo dan en el vestuario antes de que salgan a hacer una entrada en calor y después yo lo como durante la entrada en calor.
每当他们带着东西进来时，他们就像一个长着甜嘴的白痴。
Whenever they come in with something, they are like an idiot with a sweet beak.
Siempre donde entran con algo está como un boludo con un pico dulce.
嗯，我为什么要问你这个？
Well, why am I asking you this?
Bueno, ¿por qué te pregunto esto?
因为施耐德是球队的赞助商。
Because Schneider is the sponsor of the team.
Porque Schneider es el sponsor de la selección.
当他成为国家队的赞助商时，我们总是很困难。
It is always difficult for us when he is a sponsor of the national team.
Nos cuesta siempre que es sponsor de la selección.
阴谋集团继续工作，所以我们做得很好，我们做得很好，这就是为什么你继续在 FA 工作室陪伴我们，你的后面有一张海报
the cabal continues to work so we are doing well we are doing well and that is why you continue to accompany us here in FA studio you have a poster in the back
la cábala sigue funcionando así que venimos bien venimos bien y por eso nos sigue acompañando aquí en FA estudio usted tiene cartel atrás
霓虹灯标志
the neon sign
el cartel de Neón
在那里，在那里，看见了
There it is, there it is, there it is seen
Ahí está, ahí está, ahí se ve
我们感谢他在深受喜爱的 Afá Studio 中参与本次及更多节目。
who we thank for his presence in the beloved Afá Studio for this and more programs.
a quien le agradecemos su presencia en el querido Afá Studio por este y por más programas.
并继续这样下去。
And to continue like this.
Y a seguir así.
继续这样下去，因为它是卡巴拉，它是卡巴拉，卡巴拉带来好运，我们必须维持它
and to continue like this because it is Kabbalah, it is Kabbalah and Kabbalah brings good luck, we must sustain it
y a seguir así porque es cábala, es cábala y la cábala trae buena suerte, hay que sostenerla
好吧，说到这一点，请注意那些在纸条之后留下来的人
Well, speaking of that and this beware of the people who stayed after the note
Bueno, hablando de eso y esto ojo para la gente que se quedó después de la nota
将会有一场门票抽奖活动。
There is going to be a raffle for tickets.
va a haber un sorteo de entradas.
将会有一次抽签，两次参赛。
There is going to be an entry draw, two entries.
Va a haber un sorteo de entrada, dos entradas.
在 Afastudio 个人资料中，我将将该链接发送给我的朋友
In the Afastudio profile I am going to send that link to my friends
en el perfil de Afastudio le voy a mandar ese link a mis amigos
请继续关注 AF Estudio 的简介，因为有抽奖活动。
Stay tuned to the AF Estudio profile because there is an entry raffle.
Estén atentos al perfil de AF Estudio porque hay sorteo de entrada.
他们可以赚到它。
and they can earn it.
y se la pueden ganar.
一切看比赛。
Everything to watch games.
Todo para ver partidos.
啊，好！
Ah, good!
Ah, bien!
如果他们不是好人，他们都很好，但是给我 D，给我 D
If they're not the good ones, they're all good, but give me the D, give me the D
Si no son las buenas, son todas buenas, pero dame la D, dame la D
非常好 很好的时间表 不太冷 我们在这里 我们在十月 不 这不会很好
very nice nice schedule it's not so cold we're here we're in October no it's not going to be nice
bien lindo lindo horario no hace tanto frío ya estamos estamos en octubre no no va a estar lindo
参加伙计们，在 afa 工作室简介中会很好，我们没有要求
participate guys it will be good in the afa studio profile we don't have the requirements
participen muchachos va a estar bueno en el perfil de afa studio no tenemos los requisitos
他们在那里被发现。
They are found there.
Se encuentran ahí.
这篇文章将准确地询问您有关 Cabalas 的问题。
The post is going to ask you about cabalas precisely.
El posteo te va a preguntar por cábalas justamente.
啊，我也要说同样的事情。
Ah, I'm going to tell the same thing.
Ah, voy a contar lo mismo.
也许我会为想要的姐姐赢得它们。
Maybe I'll win them for my sister who wanted it.
A lo mejor las gano pa' mi hermana que quería la gancho.
但你不能参加。
But you can't participate.
Pero vos no podés participar a vosotros.
骰子乔斯特。
Dice Jost.
好吧，但我要说的是我看起来像她。
Okay, but I'm going to say that I look like her.
Está bien, pero voy a decir que parecípe de ella.
虽然他的姓氏相同。
Although he has the same last name.
Aunque tiene el mismo apellido.
作为？
As?
¿Cómo?
你能成为主持人吗？
Can you become a host?
¿Te podes poner host?
不，我不喜欢主人。
No, I don't like host.
No, no me gusta host.
不，前几天我看到一个有主人的人。
No, the other day I saw someone who had a host.
No, el otro día vi a alguien que tenía host.
你想要什么？
What would you prefer?
¿Qué preferirías?
我喜欢你的。
I like yours.
A mí me gusta la tuya.
¡呃？
¿Eh?
作为？
As?
¿Cómo?
我没有工作过一次，我正在努力工作。
I haven't worked once, I'm trying to work.
Ya no trabajé una vez, estoy intentando trabajar.
不，没关系，但你总是需要付费。
No, it's fine, but you always have to put a charge.
No, está bien, pero siempre hay que poner un cargo.
收费说干杯。
A charge to say cheers.
Un cargo para que diga la viva.
哦，不，不，如果我必须收费的话我喜欢主持人。
Oh, no, no, if I have to put a charge I like host.
Ah, no, no, si tengo que poner un cargo me gusta host.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
你站起来，该死的，白痴。
You get up, damn it, idiot.
Te levantas, joder, boludo.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
不，不，除了司机之外。
No, no, apart from the driver too.
No, no, aparte el conductor también.
可能是线路驱动器。
It could be the line driver.
Puede ser el chofer de línea.
外观不适合我
with the look it doesn't suit me
con la pinta no me juega de los casos
嗯，说到感恩，还要感谢贝蒂战士，因为贝蒂战士
Well, speaking of gratitude, also thank Bette Warrior, because Bette Warrior
Bueno, y hablando de agradecimiento, también agradecerle a Bette Warrior, porque Bette Warrior
他让我们进来、玩耍和展示，他也是 FA Estudio 的赞助商。
He tells us to come in, play and demonstrate and is also a sponsor of FA Estudio.
nos dice entrar, jugar y demostrar y es además sponsor de FA Estudio.
全年与我们同在
and is with us all year round
y está junto a nosotros durante todo el año
他们告诉我，它落后了，它落后了。
It's behind, they tell me, it's behind.
está atrás, me dicen, está atrás.
看，看。
Look, look.
Mira, mira.
是的，就在这里。
Yes, it's here.
Sí, está acá.
听着，我要射精了，我要离开他，听着。
Look, I'm going to cum and I'm going to leave him, look.
Mira, me voy a me voy a correr y le voy a dejar, mira.
这！
This!
¡Esto!
这！
This!
¡Esto!
那里！
There!
¡Ahí!
所以我要逃离他，让一切都远离他。
So I'm going to run, so that everything runs.
Para que le voy a correr, para que le corra todo.
小心哪一个，已经是这样了。
Be careful which one, this is already the case.
Ojo con cual, esto ya es así.
是的，就是这样。
Yes, this is how it is.
Ya, esto es así.
就在那里。
There it is.
Ahí está.
你看多美，你看海报拍出来多美，非凡。
Look how beautiful, look how beautiful the poster turned out, extraordinary.
Mira que lindo, mira que lindo cartel quedo, extraordinario.
好吧，Bedwarrion 赞助商，赞助商，抱歉。
Well, Bedwarrion the sponsor, the sponsor, sorry.
Bueno, Bedwarrion el sponsor, el sponsor, perdón.
谁与我们在一起并陪伴我们一整年，结束我们的特别计划
who is with us and accompanies us all year in this closing of the special program that we have had
que está junto a nosotros y nos acompaña todo el año en este cierre de programa especial que hemos tenido
他们要求喝他。
They ask to drink him.
piden herberle.
我们向塞巴斯蒂安·费尔南德斯先生致以拥抱，他今天因工作原因未能出席
We send a hug to Mr. Sebastián Fernández who has not been able to come due to his obligations today
Les mandamos un abrazo al señor Sebastián Fernández que no ha podido venir por sus obligaciones el día de hoy
但他将重新融入我们的 Metier。
but that he is going to be reintegrating into our Metier.
pero que se va a estar reintegrando a nuestra Metier.
你玩得开心吗？
Did you have a good time?
¿La pasó bien?
不不不，超级好。
No, no, super good.
No, no, súper bien.
你和国家队主帅相处得好吗？
Did you get along with the national team coach or not?
¿Se caló con el entrenador de selección o no?
是的，有一点是的。
Yes, a little bit yes.
Sí, un poquito sí.
有点冷，冷，对吗？
A little cold, cold, right?
Un poquito de chucho, chucho de frío, ¿no?
另外，不，我从来没有面试过。
Besides, no, I have never interviewed.
Aparte no, yo no he entrevistado nunca.
你知道这有多奇怪，但我要告诉你一些关于阿根廷足球的事情，我说，阿根廷足球的事情现在要进入其中，
You see, it's strange, but I'm going to tell you something about Argentine soccer, I said, I'm going to get into it now about Argentine soccer and
como raro viste pero yo te voy a decir algo la del fútbol argentino dije la va a meter ahora lo de fútbol argentino y
我沉默了。
And I was silent.
Y hice silencio.
他就进去了。
And there he entered.
Y ahí entró.
“我喜欢图库曼，”切说。
I liked Tucumán, Che said.
Me gustó Tucumán, dijo Che.
萨巴图库曼。
Tucumán de Saba.
下次我们邀​​请来自萨巴胡拉坎 (Saba Huracan) 的图库曼 (Tucumán Tucumán)，阿根廷国家队的哪一位艺术家不是别人呢？
Next we have Tucumán Tucumán from Saba Huracán. What artist in Argentine national team mode is none other?
Nosotros la próxima tenemos Tucumán Tucumán de Saba Huracán ¿Qué artista en modo selección argentina que no es otro?
不，好吧，不，没关系。
No, well, no, it's fine.
No, bueno, no, está bien.
快看，快看沙拉，路上热起来了。
Look, look at the salad, the road is heating up.
Mira, mira la ensalaza, se calienta la vía.
他没有扔，抱歉，如果...不，不，没关系，但我要向你解释一些事情。
He doesn't throw, sorry if... No, no, it's okay but I'm going to explain something to you.
No lanza, disculpe si... No, no, está bien pero le voy a explicar algo.
我不是从我家来的。
I don't come from my house.
No vengo de mi casa.
啊，好的，准备好了。
Ah, okay, ready.
Ah, está bien, listo.
现在我要和你争论 你必须有一套西装 我不会直接争论
Now I'm going to argue with you You have to have a suit I'm not going to argue directly
Ahora voy a discutir con usted Usted tiene que tener un traje No voy a discutir directamente
不，兰扎先生。
No, Mr. Lanza.
No, señor Lanza.
另一次我也来了...啊，因为我也来自...
The other time I also came... Ah, because I also came from...
La otra vez también vine... Ah, porque venía también del...
先生，这不太好，但是是的
and well sir it's not good but yes
y bueno señor no está bien pero si
不，因为今天我穿这一件是因为我必须脱掉这一件。
No, because today I wore this one because I had to go from this one.
No, porque hoy me puse esta porque tenía que ir de esta.
没关系，没关系。
It's okay, it's okay.
Está bien, está bien.
好吧，阿曼多，你已经知道了。
Well, Armando, you already know.
Bueno, Armando, usted ya sabe.
别打扰我。
Don't bother me.
No me faje.
下面他把主要...不，准备好了，准备好了。
And below he puts the ma... No, ready, ready.
Y abajo pone la ma... No, listo, listo.
庞...
Pon...
他们把手放在上面，他们给了我狗屎。我们结束了，我们要感谢亚历杭德罗·罗马努奇先生和整个吉萨团队。
They put their hand on it and they are giving me shit. We close, we are going to thank Mr. Alejandro Romanucci and the entire Giesa team.
le ponen la mano y me están cagando a puteadas cerramos le vamos a agradecer al señor Alejandro Romanucci y a todo el equipo de Giesa
他曾与莱昂内尔·德卡洛尼先生在一起，而莱昂内尔·德卡洛尼先生则与心爱的尼古拉斯·诺韦洛一起来自迈阿密。
who has been with Mr. Leonel de Caloni, who has been from Miami with the beloved Nicolás Novello.
que ha estado al señor Leonel de Caloni, que ha estado desde Miami junto al querido Nicolás Novello.
感谢你们所有人，感谢哈维尔·兰扎先生，感谢这批货物的成功，感谢你们
thanks to all of you, to Mr. Javier Lanza, the pop of this of this shipment, and to you
gracias a todos ustedes, al señor Javier Lanza, el pop de este de este envío, y a usted
我们一定会在纪念碑上见到你。
and we will surely see you at the Monumental.
y nos vemos en el Monumental seguramente.
那里见。
See you there.
Nos vemos ahí.
周二。
On Tuesday.
El día martes.
是的，拿走，拿走。
Yes, take it, take it.
Sí, llévelo, llévelo.
等我老了我就会回来
I'll be back when I'm older
我不需要知道真相。
I don't need to know the truth.
No necesito saber la verdad.
我我
i i